[Music]
[Música]
Okay, listen to one thing, listen to one
bueno escúchame una cosa escúchame una
thing, Jordi Gual did
cosa que jordi gual ha hecho una
another interview with Frank Cuesta. From
entrevista otra vez a frank cuesta desde
here we send our regards to Frank
aquí le mandamos un saludo a frank
Cuesta, who is a 100% Franco supporter, he
cuesta que por ciento franquista nos
often mentions his live shows that he
menciona muchas veces sus directos estos
does now in tweets where he says he
que hace ahora en tweets que dice que
sees us and sees us. Greetings, Frank,
nos ve y nos ve es un saludo frank
let's see what he said about himself. Let's
vamos a ver qué ha dicho sobre él
first see what he said
sobre vamos a ver primero qué ha dicho
about the YouTubers in Andorra and then
sobre los youtuber en andorra y luego
we'll see how he criticizes Mediaset. And they
vamos a ver cómo critica a mediaset y me
tell me that in the middle they tell me that in the
dicen que de por medio me dicen que de
middle
por medio
to comment, I'll say Montero. So here's
a comentar lo diré montero así que aquí
a little bit of a
un poquito
jerk,
canijo
Fran's mother, this is your super fan. Well, Frank
la madre de fran este es tu súper fan
Cuesta told me, Frank told me, tell me, come on,
bueno me dijo frank cuesta me dijo frank
and we're going to make like a video that we
cuenta y vamos a hacer como un vídeo que
were going to make. Well, I can say it
íbamos a hacer bueno lo puedo decir
because in the end, take it out or not, it was going to
porque al final sacársela o no íbamos a
be a video for Christmas. He
ser con un vídeo para navidad que me
asked me, don't make a big deal, Frank Cuesta asked me,
pidió no sea una movida me pidió frank
and in the end, let me adjust the
cuesta y al final dejarme que ajuste la
camera a little. In the end, it was canceled. No,
cámara un poco al final se canceló no
but he told me that Fran's mother put it on
pero me dijo que la madre lo puso en
Twitter. In fact, his mother  He asked
twitter de hecho que la madre le pidió
so he would like me to make him a member,
así que quisiera que le hiciera miembro
upload the two no no no upload it to javi to
sube la los dos no no lo suba a javi a
javier who said well let's see let's
javier que dijo bueno vamos a ver vamos
see what happens if there is a problem but it
a ver qué sale si hay un problema pero
is sexist in the army that the
es machista en el ejército que el
ministry of defense deals with it
ministerio de defensa se ocupe de ello
that the ministry of the interior of other
que el ministerio de interior de otras
things etcetera etcetera not to create a
cosas etcétera etcétera no crear un
ministry spending public money which is
ministerio gastando pasta pública que es
a chiringuito these are chiringuitos
un chiringuito estas son chiringuitos
subsidies that come and go that you don't
subvenciones que van y vienen que tú no
even understand how the [ __ ] public money
entiendes ni cómo el dinero público
and then then they complain that the
y luego luego se quejan de que los
youtubers go to Andorra well I have
youtubers se vayan a andorra pues que yo
not left because look but also
no me he ido porque mira pero también a
sometimes I understand you know that it is for what they
veces entiendo sabes que os está para lo
are using sometimes it is hard or I mean it
que están utilizando a veces duras o sea
is moved by what Rocito does,
está movida por lo de rociíto
his ministry I do not quite understand it
su ministerio no lo acabo de entender
because because it is critical
porque porque es crítico
we are creating the last society of
estamos creando la última sociedad de
hypocrisy in which the stupid
hipocresía en la cual se premia el tonto
suck-up is awarded that is what is awarded if now they are giving
chupamedias es lo que se premia si ahora
awards the smart lady of the
andan los premios la señora lista de la
wife of the ponytail the wife of churches
mujer del coletas la mujer de iglesias
some awards I do
unos premios
not know what the [ __ ] is to them
no sé qué hostias que les es
I had already spoken in his ministry I do
yo ya había hablado en su ministerio no
not  I just sincerely understood that your
lo acabo de entender sinceramente su
ministry doesn't know how to understand you, it's not a
ministerio no la sabe entender no es un
ministry to give you a
ministerio para darle un puesto de
job, a ministry that they have
trabajo un ministerio que se han
literally invented,
inventado ya literalmente se tiene que
nothing has to be understood there, Irene
entender nada ahí el ministerio de irene
Montero's ministry is a ministry that they
montero es un ministerio que se
invented to give you a
inventaron para darle un puesto de
job, period, there is no more,
trabajo punto pelota a no hay más
540 million euros it costs
540 millones de euros cuesta
and now they give an award to the documentary of
y ahora le da un premio al documental de
the rosita because they are committed to
la rosita porque están comprometidos con
gender violence when a
la violencia de género cuando un
documentary that they have made for an agreement
documental que han hecho por un acuerdo
to remove me from a lawsuit from
de quitarme a una demanda de
the sentence when Antonio
la sentencia de cuando antonio los
sued them, no, and now your complaint is that what they
demandó no y ahora tu queja te que lo
are saying precisely, no, now
que están diciendo precisamente no ahora
you who stopped us youtubers from
tú que dejaste de que los youtubers nos
going to Andorra,
vayamos a andorra
taking away half of what we
quitando aquí la mitad la mitad de lo
normally generate, I think that
que generamos normalmente creo que todo
in all 23 ministries, an
en 23 ministerios hay que darle un
award should be given to documentaries like that of Marta
premio a documentales como el de marta
del Castillo in some brutal work and
del castillo en algún trabajo brutal y
Simón in the bureaucratic one, it is a mess and that would have
simón en el burocrático es un lío y eso
deserved more
sí que hubiera merecido más
recognition and that the minister that the
reconocimiento y que la ministra que el
government gives it more cane,
gobierno le dé hay más caña
that issue does not die, no, that issue does not
ese tema no que no muera ese tema no que
die in oblivion, no  no the
no muera en el olvido este tema no no el
issue rosito your incredible injury before
tema rosito tu increíble lesión ante
country of country of lies country of
país de país de mentira de país de
cardboard country of tambourine country
cartulina país de pandereta país de
circus I mean it is incredible ministry of
circo o sea es increíble ministerio de
equality I have said many times about
igualdad yo lo he dicho muchas veces lo
equality let's see treat if there is
de igualdad vamos a ver tratar si hay
any problem in each of the
algún problema en cada uno de los
sections but if there is a problem to
apartados pero si hay un problema a
lose is sexist in the army that the
perder es machista en el ejército que el
ministry of defense deals with it
ministerio de defensa se ocupe de ello
so that the ministry of the interior of
para que el ministerio de interior de
other things etcetera etcetera not to create
otras cosas etcétera etcétera no crear
a wine is to have the ministry that they have
un vino es tener al ministerio que se
invented in ministry that is not
han inventado en ministerio que no hace
necessary spending public money that is a
falta gastando pasta pública que es un
chiringuito they are chiringuitos
chiringuito son chiringuitos
that come and go that you do not understand
que van y vienen que tú no entiendes
but gordo chiquito is
pero gordo chiquito
a little luxury some rolls
es un chiquito de lujo unos rollos
public money and then a chiringuito
dinero público y luego un chiringuito
of the espanyol this not of tony cantó is a
del espanyol este no de tony cantó es un
chiringuito too that would already screw me the
chiringuito también que ya me jodería la
best wound they can criticize him it is
mejor herida le pueden criticar lo es
as if it would be worth if you have to
como si valdría si hay que hay que
lead by example you
predicar con el ejemplo
have to lead by example to
hay que predicar con el ejemplo de
get there you put a chiringuito to
llegar ahí le pones un chiringuito al
toni cantó there in the pp of madrid
toni cantó ahí en el pp de madrid
my god what is left for us what is left for us
dios mío que nos queda que nos queda
but
pero
then they complain that the youtuber is
luego se quejan de que el youtuber se
going to Andorra well I haven't left
vayan a andorra pues que yo no me he ido
because look but also sometimes I
porque mira pero también a veces
understand you know why it will have gone the
entiendo sabes que porque nos habrá ido
same for us as for what
igual que para lo que
these people
éstos
said that the blond said he is leaving now and
dijeron que dijo el rubio se va ahora
also it came out like this people were talking on
para además salió así la gente hablaba
social networks for Andorra
las redes sociales para andorra
now they pay more taxes than you your
ahora pagan más impuestos que tú tu
father your father's brother your mother
padre el hermano de tu padre tu madre
new was bad in life same for
nueva era mala en la vida mismo durante
three lives she has already paid those taxes
tres vidas ya ha pagado esos impuestos
in Spain now she wants to go to Andorra it's
en españa ahora se quiere ir a andorra
not that I am I
no es que está
live in Thailand what am I
yo vivo en tailandia yo que estoy
doing I also do that
haciendo yo hago también
houses are not cheap
que las casas no son baratas los
rents
alquileres
of course a person like me might
claro a una persona como a mí a lo mejor
not be interested and is living ra
no le interesaría y está viviendo ra
because maybe what I am going to spend
porque a lo mejor lo que me voy a gastar
of what I save in taxes maybe I am
de lo que me ahorra de impuestos a lo
not going to have to spend on
mejor no lo voy a tener que gastar en la
housing because housing is
vivienda porque la vivienda es
much more expensive than here I think I
muchísimo más cara que aquí creo que
pay in Seville and the rent is paid and
pago en sevilla y se paga el alquiler y
such it will be because in Spain they do not help him and
tal será porque en españa no le ayudan y
I still understand people saying it is that they do
yo lo sigo entendiendo la gente diciendo
not pay 50 percent they do
es que es que no pagan un 50 por ciento
not pay it  50 percent as it goes by
no lo pagan un 50 por ciento como va por
sections after a certain amount of money, it
tramos después de un dinero tal paso
has the dramas that are
tiene lo de los dramas que es una
[ __ ], look, for the first section, a
gilipollez mira para el primer tramo una
person who earns
persona que gane
ten thousand euros a month, who generates
sus diez mil euros al mes que genere sus
ten thousand euros a month, that a YouTube was
diez mil euros al mes que un youtube era
the best,
lo mejor
well, not very big, it's not very big, a
bueno no muy grande no es muy grande una
person who already generates ten thousand
persona de que ya genere sus 10 mil
euros a month,
euritos al mes
the first section at
el primer tramo
47, 47% reaches
al tramo de los 47 del 47% llega en
how much
cuánto
in the middle of the year
a la mitad del año
if it's ten thousand euros and it's from
si son diez mil euros y es a partir de
sixty, in the middle of the year, from
los sesenta en la mitad del año a partir
the middle of the year, then the rest is
de la mitad del año pues ya el resto la
half, but it's not that, it's that
mitad pero es que no es eso es que
apart from the fact that already in the first sections
aparte de que ya en los primeros tramos
and a good jab, it's not
también y un buen puyazo también no es
half, but well, put the first month at
la mitad pero bueno ponle el primer mes
19, but the rest of the mission is
19 pero ya el resto de misión
twenty-something, thirty-something, put
veintitantos un treinta y tantos pone
an average that they have taken away 30, 30
una media de que te han quitado un 30 30
and so much in the first six months, well, it
y tanto en los primeros seis meses que
's fine, I think that if I would
bueno está bien yo yo creo que sí lo
leave it at 30, they wouldn't leave, dude, leave it
dejara con 30 no se irían tío
at 30, no, Syria
dejar en un 30 no siria
but even so, even so, let's see
pero así todo así todo vamos a ver por
why he extended he has to pay so much
qué extendió tiene que pagar tanto
money that the lady is hunting
dinero a que la señora está montero de
some prizes and it will be the money that he
unos premios y será el dinero que él
earns because he has a skill to
gana porque tiene una habilidad para
earn money to me that he explains to me that
ganar dinero a mí que me lo explique que
you want to go to achieve or yes yes a
te quieres ir a lograr o sea sí sí un
guy with a beard we have to call him María
tío con barba hay que llamarle maría
Isabel
isabel
let's see what he said
a ver vamos a ver qué es lo que ha dicho
about Mediaset
de mediaset
that will
que
be in three years five years
esté dentro de tres años cinco años
this is like risto it is that he is like risto it is that it
este es como risto es que es como risto
touches the lazy ones completely
es que le toca a los flojos del todo
after loving son tip you can
después de amar hijo punta le puedes
hit him with a thumbtack in the ass
pegar con una chincheta en el culo no
hackers do not bleed to me the difference is
sangran los hacker a mí la diferencia es
that it seems to me that what I do not like about
que me parece que lo que no me gusta de
this is that it goes on without
esto es que va dando sin elecciones
moral choices and at least the other but that that that
morales y al menos el otro pero eso eso
because working for me it is already
eso porque trabajar para mí ya se
understood if you work this measure has been
entiende si trabajas esta medida se ha
seen four days of the program
visto cuatro días del programa me
they made me to give it to him in the ass to you
hicieron para darle por culo el a ti
four days of the program yes four days
cuatro días del programa sí cuatro días
of the program of Frank de la Jungla it is
del programa de frank de la jungla es
true there
verdad
I go out there I went out at least I
hay salir yo ahí salí yo al menos lo
can put it because the copyright is going to jump on me
puedo poner porque me va a salta el
because well they gave me
copyright porque bueno me dieron el
permission to
permiso para
and they
y
gave me permission to
me dieron el permiso para
publish it, they have
poder publicarlo
already given me a notable
ya me han tirado ya notable
or have it in the main
o lo tengan en principal
if what I see them and there I also had
si lo que les vea y ahí también tuve yo
my way on television
mi camino en la tele
if they have not thrown me to see me in life
si no me han tirado a verme en la vida
everything is a lie in the program there is no
todo es mentira en el programa no hay
right here I am here I am look
derecho aquí estoy aquí estoy yo mira
here I am here I am making my
aquí estoy yo aquí estoy haciendo mi
truck
camión
in 2019 in 2019 I will change for this
en 2019 en 2019 ya me cambio por esto
that focus so much on the roof the same is
que enfoque tanto para el techo igual es
a product
un producto
with Marta Flich and life here they
con la marta flich y vida aquí me
present me like this youtuber
presentan de narices como este youtuber
who explains to us why
que nos explica por qué el vídeo de
Frank's video is a person and this youtuber is
frank es una persona y este youtuber es
this
este
the youtuber javi oliveira accused Frank
el youtuber javi oliveira acusó a frank
de la jungle of falsifying the attack of the
de la jungla de falsear el ataque del
front that
frente que
sat like the ass this video made me
le sentó como el culo este vídeo me hizo
a video saying I do
un vídeo diciendo
n't know what we had there is a scuffle that is
no sé qué tuvimos hay un rifirrafe que
going on today cool you have seen that it makes me
hay en día guay ya habéis visto que me
laugh I do raid I think he went
hace reír hago raid creo que se pasó con
a little too far with Dallas he I don't remember what
dallas un poco él no me acuerdo que le
Dallas said to him but I remember where
dijo dallas a él pero me acuerdo donde
Frank costs quite badly towards the buoy
frank cuesta bastante feo hacia la boya
and crossed the  line
y traspasaba traspasaba la línea alguna
something is that you remember us
cosa es que esté acuérdate de nosotros
when you make the jump on tv javi
cuando pegues el salto en la tele javi
for that will never happen keep saying to
para eso nunca pasará seguí diciendo a
my youtube channel I will always be there
mi canal de youtube seguiré siempre ahí
if they call me for a program to
si me llaman para un programa para
collaborate or whatever no no I have never
colaborar o lo que sea yo no no nunca he
said no it
dicho que no
is also Italian to see things that they
también es italiano a ver cosas que me
put me like things that you know what
pongan a mí como cosas que ya sabéis qué
type of programs that I don't like but
tipo de programas que no me gustan pero
an ana rosa program
un programa de ana rosa'
and in 2019 it
y en 2019
could be that
podría ser que
a while ago if all with
hace un tiempo si todos con
conditionals it was all conditional then it
condicionales era todo condicional pues
could be said that we have
podría ser se diría que tenemos a
someone who has talked about doing nothing hey
alguien que ha hablado de hacer nada de
this is not a statement
oye esto no es ninguna afirmación
no statement
ninguna afirmación
I don't know if I have seen it he has a
yo no se lo haber visto tiene una
family he has children he has to give his
familia tiene unos hijos tiene que darle
children a place and his job is they
lugar a los hijos y su trabajo es
work for mediaset okay he has his
trabajan para mediaset vale tiene su
own criteria but we say what was
propio criterio pero decimos lo que fue
ridiculous about risto was when he did the
ridículo de risto fue cuando hizo el
debate with roma man when he did the
debate con roma tío cuando hizo el
debate with roja yes of course us
debate con roja sí claro que nosotros
but about the jungle that if the video that
pero de la jungla que si el vídeo que no
was not little the
era poquita el
merit of his work or what I do the
mérito a su trabajo o lo que hago los
animals and so on and above all the world
animales y demás y sobre todo el mundo
no I have not followed his career much
no no he seguido mucho su trayectoria
but it would be all the  world has a lot of
pero sería todo el mundo lo tiene mucho
respect and a lot of affection for frank my
respeto y mucho cariño a frank mis
videos are never intended that way
vídeos nunca van con la intención así
at that time it was more beastly the best
que en esa época era más bestia lo mejor
I don't but it was agreed that it was
yo no pero era acuerdo que era
humorous my intention valera was no
humorístico mi intención valera no era
other than politics of carmen in fact me
otra que política del carmen de hecho yo
because I said damn but it escalated less and
porque yo decía pero escaló menos y
maybe this video well it can be
a lo mejor el vídeo este pues puede ser
more or less acting or whatever but that does
más o menos actúa o lo que sea pero eso
n't take away from the fact that he is interpreting a
no quita que está interpretando una
real scene or on another occasion in which it
escena real o en otra ocasión en la que
was real whatever it is no but it is
haya sido de verdad lo que sea no pero
true it is that they fought like
es que es verdad es que peleaban como
the power rangers this video
los power rangers este vídeo
as soon as they bring up topics he called me he called me he
en cuanto le meten temas a mí me llamó a
said fine I'm at
mí me llamó él me dijo bien estoy por lo
least he said fine this do you want to talk
menos me dijo bien esto quieres hablar
about it I said no that's it but this is coming to me
de ello dije no ya está pero me viene
mediaset is a steamroller I
mediaset es una máquina apisonadora es
mean they offered me
decir a mí me ofrecieron
a story when yasser I said no
una historia cuando yasser dije que no
again and what happened is that after two
otra vez y que pasó que a las dos
weeks they were crushing me halfway through that do
semanas me estaban machacando medias esa
you think that was some kind of
tu crees que eso era una especie de
revenge for not accepting an offer
venganza por no aceptar una oferta
man is it revenge for leaving there
hombre es una venganza por irme de allí
and he doesn't want to come back
y no quiere volver
but now I was in halfway through on
pero ahora estaba en medias en el
frank's jungle show  It was in
programa de frank de la jungla era en
media c
media c
frank de la jungla was called if it was 4 it
frank de la jungla se llamaba si era 4
wasn't 4 of course it
no era 4 claro
was 4 it's true I did it on another
era 4 es verdad lo hacía yo en otro
program
programa
and more will come to me and more will
y más que me vendrán y más que me
come to me you think that the
vendrán tú piensa que el programa de
frank de la jungla program they still put on
frank de la jungla nos siguen poniendo
today it's a program from ten
hoy en día es un programa de hace diez
years ago programming the [ __ ] day put well
años programando el día puesto pues
I was a gold mine and it would have been
yo era un filón de dinero y hubiera
a gold mine because a
sería un filón de dinero porque un
program like that because you reached
programa de la vía porque llegabas a
a lot of people sitting in family rooms
muchísima gente sentada salas familiares
and they are animals and there is a connection and there won't be
y son animales y hay una conexión y no
another one like it that one can come out that
va a haber otro igual que puede salir
does this later but one like that won't come
uno que haga esto después pero no te va
out for you because you've never
a salir uno igual porque jamás has
had a guy who is in the place where it's
tenido un tío que esté en el lugar donde
animal and takes you it's that you haven't
está animal y te lo coja es que no has
had it
tenido
then that screwed them up that I left but it did
entonces eso les jodió que me fui pero
n't leave day basile me after having
no dejó día basile yo después de haber
left mediaset I continued going to have
dejado mediaset me seguido yendo a tomar
coffee with basile and I have no problem with
café con basile y no tengo problema con
him and then he kills you from behind there
él y luego por detrás te mata
are no more coffees after this no no yes yes yes me me
ya no hay más cafés después de esto ya
today basile is one of
no no sí sí sí yo yo hoy basile es de
the few who called to ask how
los pocos que llamaba a preguntarse cómo
I was I arrived watch out you then your son
estaba yo llegué ojo usted luego su hijo
of a [ __ ] then he is a demon but
de luego él es un demonio pero
because his job is to make money with
porque es su trabajo es hacer dinero con
television I only understand but
la televisión yo sólo entiendo pero
ready he is not that bad you have seen
listo no es tan malo el han visto la
people have a lot of mania because it is like
gente tiene mucha manía porque es como
he gives a speech and then does
que él da un discurso y luego hacerlo
the opposite he is like the typical
hace lo contrario es como el típico sido
moralist and such that he gives you
moralista y tal que te va dando
lessons but the rest will retire
lecciones pero el resto se retirarán
write to a fan of books and we will
escribir a un fan de libros y le
understand him we can all stop this and he
entenderemos todos podemos parar esto y
is a very strange guy he is a very strange guy
es un tío muy raro es un tío muy raro
but he is a guy who is very what I do not
pero es un tío que es muy lo que no
understand about France because he always
entiendo de francia porque siempre se
dresses exactly the same
viste exactamente igual
like a bar without sound some kind of
como bar sin sonido algún tipo de
claim or has some kind of
reivindicación o tiene algún tipo de
symbolism or meaning or something like that you
simbología o de significado o algo por
can tell me kids but it
el estilo me podeis decir chavales pero
always existed for many years always
existía siempre muchos años siempre
dressed exactly the same the cap the
vestido exactamente igual la gorra la
white t-shirt the shorts the
camiseta blanca el pantalón corto la
croc is something to have in the closet a
croc es algo que tener en el armario un
lot of identical clothes not to do
montón de ropa iguales no para hacer
this it is some kind of symbol made as
esto es algún tipo de símbolo hecho como
different in the personal than the
diferente en lo personal que lo
professional I mean he is
profesional
a guy he is a sweet guy it
o sea es un tío es un tío dulce
emerged that risto mejide joe surprise efe
surgió que risto mejide joe sorpresa efe
is a sweet guy you know him
es un tío dulce tú lo conoces
personally then you have had dealings you have
personalmente entonces has tenido trato
had dealings with him and you do not  you felt
has tenido trato con él y no te sentiste
when what happened happened the last
cuando pasó lo que pasó lo último
bit betrayed because as much
traicionado un poquito porque por mucho
as I warned you to do to say go
que te avise a realizar para decir tiró
ahead a home of course if we have the
p'alante un hogar claro si tenemos el
script we have two or three conversations
guión tenemos dos o tres conversaciones
pending but with a coffee and him
pendientes pero con un café y él
talking about how an organist and me as
hablando de como organista y yo como
frank you have I understand how the television thing goes
frank tienes yo entiendo cómo va el tema
I understand it is that I
de la televisión yo lo entiendo es que
understand television is a
lo entiendo la televisión es un
show and sometimes you have to do
espectáculo y a veces tienes que hacer
things that maybe you don't like
cosas que a lo mejor no te gustan
especially baptize programs like the one
especialmente bautice programas como el
he has everything is a lie everything is
que él tiene todo es mentira todo es
true boy he has a family I
verdad chico él tiene una familia yo lo
understand that it hurts
entiendo que hace daño
because the nonsense ex phrase I take it very
pues la tontería ex frase lo tomo muy en
seriously that very much to heart as a
serio eso muy a pecho como un ataque
super serious attack and with the years that he has been
súper grave y con los años que lleva
working in television he knows what
trabajando en televisión que sabe de lo
the move is about
que va la movida
I understand other types of attacks
yo entiendo otro tipo de ataques ataques
personal attacks when they invade your privacy
personales cuando invaden tu intimidad
when they violate your honor but he
cuando vulneran tu honor pero eso se lo
took that super badly the agreement with us we
tomó super mal el acuerdo con nosotros
took it super super badly and I'm dying the
lo tomamos super super mal y me muero el
tri that put him to give it that he went over the top of
tri que le puso a darla que se pasó de
the marinera cloth and he didn't apologize I think at
la marinera tela y no se disculpó creo a
that rate cloth
ese paso tela
and what you do is false prove it to me  I
y lo que haces es falso demuéstramelo o
mean tell me how do you do it tell me how do you
sea dime que como haces tú dime como
catch this bug how did you get close to
coges tu este como te acercaste a
a lion how do you do this I mean it makes you
un león como haces esto es decir te hace
people can do whatever harm
que la gente te puede hacer el daño que
you want them to do to you if I had
tú quieras que te haga si yo me hubiera
gotten into a fight with them and tried to
metido a pelear con ellos y a intentar
debate but I have nothing to debate
debatir pero yo tengo que debatir nada
I've experienced it I've shown it to you you
yo lo he vivido yo os lo he enseñado
want to prove it take it
vosotros queréis demostrar eso
apart you mean he's already wearing
desmontarlo quieres decir que ya lleva
makeup here from a bite take it
un maquillaje aquí de una mordedura
apart look for a makeup artist now with
desmonta lo busca maquillador ahora con
the producer then they made a
la productora entonces hicieron un
four day program and insinuating
programa de cuatro días e insinuante
things about makeup I mean a whole
cosas de maquillaje o sea que toda una
fiction let's say it deserves even a
ficción vamos que merece siquiera una
fiction then you say why am
ficción entonces dices para que me voy a
I going to get into a fight with his gray eyesight that's why there was
meter yo a pelear con de su vista canas
a there
por eso hubo un
was no moment to say he
no hubo ningún momento de decir los
called them and I [ __ ] on their dead
llamó y me cago en sus muertos
frank be
frank
careful there are powers here
el cuidado que hay poderes aquí
okay you don't have to because it's a
vale no tienes por qué porque es una
television a television is more
televisión una televisión es más
powerful than me I can't start
poderosa que yo yo no puedo
fighting with Mediaset
pelearme con mediaset
I can ignore them and say no look I would
yo puedo pasar de ellos y decir no mira
n't have anything for example go up call
no tendría nada por ejemplo subir llamar
or whatever and give everything and listen to me this
o lo que sea y dar todo y escúchame esto
seems  so but this is treated listen to
parece así pero esto está tratada oye a
your opinion nothing would happen no it's already
tu opinión tampoco pasaría nada no ya
but it has a power that I don't
está pero tiene un poder que yo no lo
have I have power in my environment okay
tengo yo tengo poder en mi entorno vale
but I have the power to watch a
pero yo tengo el poder ver una
television to monitor and sound mediaset is
televisión a vigilar y sonar mediaset me
going to try to crush me crush me and if I
va a intentar apisonar apisonar y si yo
enter I'm dead if I don't enter I
entro estoy muerto si yo no entro yo
take it and say I say whatever I want I've
cojo y digo digo lo que quiera yo lo he
done it and that's it you understand if I fight
hecho y ya está entiendes si yo me peleo
with you on the internet you have the odds against you
contigo en internet tú tienes las de
because you have a much
ganar porque tienes una expansión mucho
larger expansion you have much more
más grande tú tienes mucha más
experience and you know how to move better
experiencia y sabes cómo moverte mejor
between grit yeah but the number don't be afraid that we
entre grit ya pero el número no tema que
see the newspaper when we had
vemos el diario cuando nosotros tuvimos
here pulse with drugs I
aquí a pulso con droga
was nervous but had to do the same thing
estaba nervioso pero tuvo hacer lo mismo
in another way because because you have
de otra manera porque porque tú tienes
much more power then I already learned
mucho más poder entonces yo ya aprendí
that in certain fights I have nothing to
que en ciertas peleas yo no tengo nada
do and it's not worth it because it's
que hacer y no merece la pena porque es
a waste of time energy
una pérdida de tiempo de energía
and nothing
y nada
if I don't see that is in
si yo no ver eso está en agentes
social agents have said this is many times it
sociales han dicho esto es muchas veces
sends you air today they commented on this about you
te manda aire hoy comentaron esto de ti
today I commented okay well what do you want is that it
hoy comentaba vale pues que quieres es
was not a thing like super
que tampoco era una cosa como súper
super cold experts already this
súper fría expertos ya está éste
presents better or worse dependence that
presenta mejor o peor dependencia que te
catches you but  let's go to the end with the
pille pero vamos al final cabo con el
tone in which I was we are not going to
tono en el que estaba yo no vamos a
be the old videos already tedious it
estar los vídeos antiguos ya tediosa no
was not a bad tone it was not a super
era un tono malo no era un tono súper
warrior tone on the contrary you understand me more
guerrero al contrario me entienden a más
humorous than anything else what do
humorístico que otra cosa que opinen
you think family there you will be in the
ustedes familia ahí estaréis en la caja
comment box by the way important the
de comentario por cierto importante los
two the two videos that upload the
dos los dos vídeos que subir el canal
main channel the last two videos that are
principal los dos últimos vídeos que hay
uploaded on the main page two gems that
subir en cara principal dos joyas que te
[ __ ] you look at it please look at it because
cagas mirarlo por favor mirarlo porque
I am not it's that [ __ ] you
no soy es que te cagas
[Music]
[Música]